var arr=[{
    Question:"Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
    Option1:"npx create-react-app appname",
    Option2:"npm install create-react-app",
    Option3:"npx install create-react-app -g",
    Option4:"install - l create-react-app",
    Answer:"npx create-react-app appname"
},{
    Question:"In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
    Option1:"Create",
    Option2:"Extends",
    Option3:"Inherits",
    Option4:"Delete",
    Answer:"Extends"
},{
    Question:"What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
    Option1:"3000",
    Option2:"8080",
    Option3:"5000",
    Option4:"3030",
    Answer:"3000"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
    Option1:"State & Props",
    Option2:"Services & Components",
    Option3:"State & Services",
    Option4:"State & Component",
    Answer:"State & Props"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
    Option1:"SetinitialComponen",
    Option2:"renderComponent",
    Option3:"render",
    Option4:"All of the above",
    Answer:"renderComponent"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
    Option1:"Compiler",
    Option2:"Transpilar",
    Option3:"Both of the above",
    Option4:"None of the above",
    Answer:"Both of the above"
},{
    Question:"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
    Option1:"SetState",
    Option2:"Render with arguments",
    Option3:"Props",
    Option4:"PropTypes",
    Answer:"Props"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
    Option1:"this.State{}",
    Option2:"this.setState",
    Option3:"this.setChangeState",
    Option4:"All of the above",
    Answer:"this.setState"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
    Option1:"self()",
    Option2:"inherits()",
    Option3:"this()",
    Option4:"super()",
    Answer:"super()"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is used to render components in web pages ?",
    Option1:"DOM_render()",
    Option2:"render()",
    Option3:"ReactDOM_render()",
    Option4:"transfer()",
    Answer:"render()"
},{
    Question:"Which function in React.js is invoked before a component gets its props reassigned ?",
    Option1:"componentWillRecieveProps()",
    Option2:"componentWillStopProps()",
    Option3:"componentWillControlProps()",
    Option4:"componentRecieveProps()",
    Answer:"componentWillRecieveProps()"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is true about key props ?",
    Option1:"'Key' props are used to look beauty",
    Option2:"'Key' prop is a way to identify the newly added element",
    Option3:"It is one type of attribute of HTML",
    Option4:"It is not used in the array",
    Answer:"'Key' prop is a way to identify the newly added element"
},{
    Question:"What is the best definition of React.js ?",
    Option1:"Server-side Framework",
    Option2:"User-interface framework",
    Option3:"A Library for building interaction interfaces",
    Option4:"None of These",
    Answer:"A Library for building interaction interfaces"
},{
    Question:"Which below function in React.js is used to get the DOM node when the component is rendered ?",
    Option1:"renderDOM()",
    Option2:"componentAtNode()",
    Option3:"getDOMNode()",
    Option4:"findDOMNode()",
    Answer:"findDOMNode()"
},{
    Question:"Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    Option1:"Virtual DOM",
    Option2:"Original DOM",
    Option3:"Both A and B",
    Option4:"None of the above",
    Answer:"Virtual DOM"
},{
    Question:"What is ReactJS",
    Option1:"Server-side library",
    Option2:"user interface library",
    Option3:"both a and b",
    Option4:"none of the above",
    Answer:"user interface library"
},{
    Question:"Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside?",
    Option1:"Render with arguments",
    Option2:"setState",
    Option3:"Propztypes",
    Option4:"props",
    Answer:"props"
},{
    Question:"Who created React.js?",
    Option1:"Jordan Mike",
    Option2:"Jordan Walke",
    Option3:"Tim Lee",
    Option4:"Jordan Lee",
    Answer:"Jordan Walke"
},{
    Question:"In which language is React.js written?",
    Option1:"python",
    Option2:"javascript",
    Option3:"java",
    Option4:"php",
    Answer:"javascript"
},{
    Question:"How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    Option1:"1",
    Option2:"2",
    Option3:"3",
    Option4:"4",
    Answer:"1"
}]
export default arr;